// Array der indeholder nummer, spørgsmål, svarmuligheder og svar for quiz1 (cocktails and drinks)
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "What is the most popular cocktail in the world?",
    answer: "Old Fashioned",
    options: [
      "Martini",
      "Daiquiri",
      "Margarita",
      "Old Fashioned"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Piña Colada is the national drink of..",
    answer: "Puerto Rico",
    options: [
      "Puerto Rico",
      "Spain",
      "Colombia",
      "Greece"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Salt, lime wheel, orange liqueur, lime juice What alcohol is missing to make a margarita?",
    answer: "Tequila",
    options: [
      "Vodka",
      "Tequila",
      "Gin",
      "White rum"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "What shaken cocktail contains : Orange peel, cocktail cherry and a sugar cube?",
    answer: "Old Fashioned",
    options: [
      "Negroni",
      "Long Island",
      "Old Fashioned",
      "Cosmopolitan"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 5,
    question: "What ingredient is added to make a plain martini become a dirty martini?",
    answer: "Olive juice",
    options: [
      "Lime",
      "More gin",
      "Olive juice",
      "Mango Liquor"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "What is the oldest known cocktail?",
    answer: "Sazerac",
    options: [
      "Negroni",
      "Old Fashioned",
      "Martini",
      "Sazerac"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "What ingredient is not typical in a Long Island Iced Tea cocktail?",
    answer: "Tea",
    options: [
      "Tea",
      "Gin",
      "Rum",
      "Tequila"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "What cocktail is served unmixed in a tall glass and is made with tequila, orange juice, and grenadine syrup?",
    answer: "Tequila Sunrise",
    options: [
      "Sex on the beach",
      "Tequila Sunrise",
      "Daiquiri",
      "Negroni"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "What are the 2 main ingredients in a Screwdriver?",
    answer: "Vodka and orange juice",
    options: [
      "Gin and apple juice",
      "Whisky and cherry",
      "Cranberry and Vermouth",
      "Vodka and orange juice"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "How does James Bond like his Martini?",
    answer: "Shaken",
    options: [
      "Stirred",
      "Shaken",
      "Without ice",
      "Wet"
    ]
  },
];